{
    "subject": "Victor_Salva",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Clownhouse",
    "human_readable": "Victor Salva created Clownhouse.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7232570648193359,
            "question": "Has Victor Salva won any awards for his work on Clownhouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5904039144515991,
            "question": "What is the name of the film that Victor Salva created?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4690055549144745,
            "question": "When was Clownhouse released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3997642397880554,
            "question": "Was Clownhouse a commercial success?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37369590997695923,
            "question": "Where was Clownhouse filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3238123655319214,
            "question": "Who directed the film Clownhouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3049992620944977,
            "question": "What is the plot of Clownhouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2903108596801758,
            "question": "What themes does Clownhouse explore?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2287008911371231,
            "question": "Is Clownhouse a horror film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1734504997730255,
            "question": "What other films has Victor Salva directed?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Victor Salva created Clownhouse.",
            "html": "yago_7079_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Clownhouse a horror film?",
            "html": "yago_7079_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What themes does Clownhouse explore?",
            "html": "yago_7079_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the plot of Clownhouse?",
            "html": "yago_7079_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7079_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7079_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7079_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7079_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7079_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7079_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7079_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7079_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7079_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7079_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I found that:\n\n* The documents mention \"Clownhouse\" and its director as Victor Salva.\n* There is no explicit statement saying that Victor Salva created Clownhouse.\n\nSo, based on this analysis, the answer is:\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references indicating that Victor Salva wrote and directed the film \"Clownhouse,\" thus supporting the statement that Victor Salva created Clownhouse."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because the context information from multiple sources indicates that Victor Salva was convicted of sexual misconduct with Nathan Forest Winters, a 12-year-old actor, during the making of Clownhouse, suggesting that he did not create the film alone or independently.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}